《越狱》前情提要
Previously on Prison Break...
我们会把你救出来的
We're gonna get you out of here.
越狱开始了  快走  快走
The escape is on. Go, go, go!
这家伙是谁
Who the hell is the guy?
他是我哥
He's my brother.
你现在不能死  迈克尔  知道吗
Can't die on me now, Michael, you know, you're gonna tell me
你得告诉我为什么我是你的得力干将
why I'm your whip hand.
我们找到迈克尔了
We found Michael.
-他伤得很重  -我得走了
- He's been busted up real bad. - I got to go.
连你自己都不知道会陷入什么麻烦中
You don't know what you'd be walking into.
这不安全
It's not safe.
我不能直视着我儿子的眼睛
I can't look my son in the eye
告诉他我本来可以尽力救他父亲
and tell him that I let his father die,
他还从没见过他父亲呢
a father he's never met.
没想到还能再见到你
Never thought I'd see this face again.
你本不该见到的
You weren't supposed to.
林肯·布鲁斯
Lincoln Burrows.
不如你出来吧
How about you step out
把欠的十万还给我们
and pay us the 100 grand you owe us.
-你很伟大  林肯  -好好休息
- There is nobility in you, Lincoln. - You should rest up.
-我们还需要你  -没想到你还会担心
- We're gonna need you. - Didn't know you worried.
该担心的我都会担心
About the right things.
怎么了
What's wrong?
是他  你老公
It's him. Your husband.
雅各布
Jacob
就是波塞冬
is Poseidon.
他是中情局特工  深度卧底
He's a CIA operative, deep cover.
他管理着一个叫做"21号空间"的地下组织
He runs a splinter cell called 21-Void.
他看中了我的能力
He targeted me for my skills.
迈克尔  他现在正和我们的儿子在一起
Michael, he's with our son right now.
我会尽快赶到美国
I'll get to the States as soon as I can.
我丈夫雅各布·奈斯
Did my husband, Jacob Ness,
有没有让你查我的手机
ask you to work on my cell phone?
他说他想找出
He said he was looking to find
跟踪他妻子的那些人
the people who were stalking his wife,
我做了深度数据追踪
so I did a data dive.
我儿子呢
Where's my son?
在我手里
I have him.
至于我需不需要用他威胁你
And whether or not I have to threaten him
这全看你要不要放下手里的枪了
is entirely contingent upon you putting the gun down.
发现卡尼尔·乌提斯
Kaniel Outis
在地中海一艘货船上
has been located on a cargo ship in the Mediterranean.
他们识破你了
They made you.
跑
Run!
地中海某处
喂  哥们
Hey, yo,
我们去哪
where we headed?
马赛
Marseille.
-马赛  -马赛
- Marseilles. - ‭Marseilles.
我欠你的  斯科菲尔德
I own you, Scofield.
六年前
你的事情我全都知道
I know everything about you.
连你最平常的小动作都知道  比如动物园
Even your most mundane actions, like the zoo.
你和动物园算怎么回事
What's with you and the zoo?
我去那里思考
I go there to think.
上个月去了十八次吗
18 times in the past month?
-真没少思考  -我在想怎么才能把你的人
- A lot of thinking. - I was figuring out how to get your guy
从巴兰基亚弄出来
out of Barranquilla.
结果发现他不仅是个叛军首领
Turns out he's not just a rebel leader--
还是个杀人不眨眼的反社会分子
he's a murderous sociopath.
舍不得孩子  套不得狼嘛
That's the only way to make omelets.
我需要更多地了解我们的目标
I need to know more about our targets.
如果我要策划越狱的话  容不得半点闪失
If I'm facilitating escapes, we can't have surprises.
你应当为之自豪  你我二人
Be proud. You and me,
-我们在改变世界  -并没有让它变得更好
- we're changing the world. - Doesn't make it right.
别搞得好像你突然之间成了安于现状的人
Don't act like you're suddenly a fan of the status quo, okay?
现在这种体制的运作又慢又蠢  注定要完蛋
The system, it's slow, stupid, and doomed to fail.
这就是当初你不得不把你哥救出来的原因
That's why you had to bust your brother out in the first place.
我上次见你之后才有的新纹身啊
New ink since the last time I saw you.
-在做新计划吗  -不  没有什么新计划
- Working on a new plan? - No. No new plan.
就是看不习惯光秃秃的皮肤
Just get tired of looking at empty skin.
你知道  当初就是在福克斯河监狱的
You know, it was those tats at Fox River
那些纹身吸引到了我的目光
that caught my eye in the first place.
我告诉自己  那个将其计划
I had to know everything about the man
纹在身上的人  我得了解他的一切
who wore his plans on his skin.
看似一览无遗  实则神秘莫测
In plain sight yet so mysterious.
实权的关键在于消失
The key to real power is to disappear.
-奈斯教授  你好  -克劳迪娅  你好
- Hi, Professor Ness. - Hello, Claudia.
实权的秘诀
Yeah, the secret to real power
在于决不违背你的意愿
is to never betray your intentions,
深藏不露
to wear nothing on your sleeve.
也决不让任何人
And to never let anyone
看见你的脸
see your face.
扫瞄已启动
图像采集
构建面部轮廓比对
检索匹配
构建匹配
身份匹配已获取
进来
Come on in.
下次我被关禁闭的时候
Next time I'm sitting in solitary,
我会想着你在这个舒服的空调屋里
I'll think of you in here, running the world
统治世界
in air-conditioned comfort.
我也是出过外勤任务的人
I've spent my time in the field.
你准备好去缅甸了吗
You all set for Myanmar?
只剩几周的时间了
It's only a few weeks off.
这就是我为什么来这的原因
That's why I'm here.
我想拉一个人入伙
I want to bring someone on board.
-真的吗  -实兑监狱[缅甸西部港市]的活儿需要两个人
- Oh, really? - ‭The prison camp at Sittwe is a two-man job.
我一直在关注这个人  他会很有用
I've been watching this guy. He'll be useful.
关注他吗  你现在居然负责招兵买马了吗
Watching him? You in charge of recruiting now?
相信我  我最不想做的就是把别人牵扯进来
Trust me. The last thing I was to do is suck someone else into this.
他会做我的后盾  加快进展
He'll have my back and he'll speed things up,
提高我们的胜算
increase our odds.
罪犯详细信息  大卫·马丁
履历并不是很出色
Not exactly a distinguished career.
他被关在监狱  是个臭脾气
He's held up well in prison. He's got a mean streak.
还是个孤儿
And he grew up without a family.
这意味着他可以被操控
It means he can be manipulated.
如果你在蓄谋什么
If you're planning something,
我总是会先你一步的
I'll always be a step ahead of you.
你懂的
You know that.
我能从你的眼神中看穿一切
I can see everything in your eyes.
眼神背后的心机才是关键
It's what's behind the eyes that counts,
教授
Professor.
那你要等我一年后想到逃出实兑的计策呢
So you're gonna wait a year for me to find my way out of Sittwe?
还是你会给我找个搭档
Or are you gonna get me a partner,
以便我们继续改变世界的大业呢
so we get on with the business of changing the world?
就这么定了
Done.
法国  马赛
我得吃点儿东西
I need some food.
我跟你一起
I'm with you.
林肯  是莎拉
Linc, it's Sara.
安全回来了  你们在哪
她回到纽约了
She's back in New York.
她和麦克还好吗
Are she and Mike okay?
我也正要问呢
That's what I'm trying to find out.
-雅各布起疑了吗
-不确定  但我们不能留在这  太危险了
别担心  我会来找你  很快  爱你
我也爱你  小麦也是
怎么了  迈克尔
What is it, Michael?
出事了
Something's wrong.
我会很快来见你
是  你会的
Yes, you will.
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
翻译     高庭玫瑰   春天里的小熊   肉塔   轩辕喵
翻译     徐棒棒   木浅   GV   四月   ABCpril    PiPi
校对     、胜天半子、的、何何、      木浅
时间轴     姜姜    大葱    查查    WEB版轴  何何、
越 狱 第五季第八集
后期     吉吉    V2版后期  、胜天半子、的、何何、
总监           、胜天半子、的、何何、
-我得立刻回美国  -等等
- I got to get back to the States. - Slow down.
你现在是卡尼尔·乌提斯  记得吗
You're Kaniel Outis, remember?
越狱     我命由我不由天！胜天半子半痴癫！
各国的禁飞名单上都有你
You're on every no-fly list in the world.
雅各布对莎拉下手了
Jacob's done something to Sara.
可能对麦克也是
Maybe Mike, too.
-你怎么知道的  -那条短信
- How do you know? - ‭That text.
人人影视Pro
■
人人影视官方唯一APP
在线观看，离线缓存，百度云
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
■
m 200 100 l 200 110 l 210 110 l 210 100 m 210 100 m 160 50 l 160 60 l 170 60 l 170 50 m 170 50 m 150 150 l 150 160 l 160 160 l 160 150 m 160 150 m 140 210 l 140 220 l 150 220 l 150 210 m 150 210 m 40 240 l 40 250 l 50 250 l 50 240 m 50 240 m 200 130 l 200 140 l 210 140 l 210 130 m 210 130 m 180 80 l 180 90 l 190 90 l 190 80 m 190 80 m 110 160 l 110 170 l 120 170 l 120 160 m 120 160 m 160 160 l 160 170 l 170 170 l 170 160 m 170 160 m 280 210 l 280 220 l 290 220 l 290 210 m 290 210 m 220 80 l 220 90 l 230 90 l 230 80 m 230 80 m 190 240 l 190 250 l 200 250 l 200 240 m 200 240 m 280 80 l 280 90 l 290 90 l 290 80 m 290 80 m 210 240 l 210 250 l 220 250 l 220 240 m 220 240 m 250 130 l 250 140 l 260 140 l 260 130 m 260 130 m 170 210 l 170 220 l 180 220 l 180 210 m 180 210 m 240 240 l 240 250 l 250 250 l 250 240 m 250 240 m 50 100 l 50 110 l 60 110 l 60 100 m 60 100 m 40 140 l 40 150 l 50 150 l 50 140 m 50 140 m 60 260 l 60 270 l 70 270 l 70 260 m 70 260 m 260 100 l 260 110 l 270 110 l 270 100 m 270 100 m 250 100 l 250 110 l 260 110 l 260 100 m 260 100 m 120 90 l 120 100 l 130 100 l 130 90 m 130 90 m 80 40 l 80 50 l 90 50 l 90 40 m 90 40 m 70 280 l 70 290 l 80 290 l 80 280 m 80 280 m 120 280 l 120 290 l 130 290 l 130 280 m 130 280 m 150 90 l 150 100 l 160 100 l 160 90 m 160 90 m 100 140 l 100 150 l 110 150 l 110 140 m 110 140 m 90 220 l 90 230 l 100 230 l 100 220 m 100 220 m 160 100 l 160 110 l 170 110 l 170 100 m 170 100 m 280 180 l 280 190 l 290 190 l 290 180 m 290 180 m 220 130 l 220 140 l 230 140 l 230 130 m 230 130 m 40 80 l 40 90 l 50 90 l 50 80 m 50 80 m 280 50 l 280 60 l 290 60 l 290 50 m 290 50 m 170 240 l 170 250 l 180 250 l 180 240 m 180 240 m 240 80 l 240 90 l 250 90 l 250 80 m 250 80 m 220 240 l 220 250 l 230 250 l 230 240 m 230 240 m 120 190 l 120 200 l 130 200 l 130 190 m 130 190 m 260 70 l 260 80 l 270 80 l 270 70 m 270 70 m 80 140 l 80 150 l 90 150 l 90 140 m 90 140 m 70 60 l 70 70 l 80 70 l 80 60 m 80 60 m 60 100 l 60 110 l 70 110 l 70 100 m 70 100 m 130 180 l 130 190 l 140 190 l 140 180 m 140 180 m 120 60 l 120 70 l 130 70 l 130 60 m 130 60 m 90 150 l 90 160 l 100 160 l 100 150 m 100 150 m 100 40 l 100 50 l 110 50 l 110 40 m 110 40 m 90 280 l 90 290 l 100 290 l 100 280 m 100 280 m 80 200 l 80 210 l 90 210 l 90 200 m 90 200 m 180 280 l 180 290 l 190 290 l 190 280 m 190 280 m 130 200 l 130 210 l 140 210 l 140 200 m 140 200 m 280 280 l 280 290 l 290 290 l 290 280 m 290 280 m 180 190 l 180 200 l 190 200 l 190 190 m 190 190 m 100 270 l 100 280 l 110 280 l 110 270 m 110 270 m 240 230 l 240 240 l 250 240 l 250 230 m 250 230 m 230 170 l 230 180 l 240 180 l 240 170 m 240 170 m 190 180 l 190 190 l 200 190 l 200 180 m 200 180 m 200 230 l 200 240 l 210 240 l 210 230 m 210 230 m 170 140 l 170 150 l 180 150 l 180 140 m 180 140 m 240 180 l 240 190 l 250 190 l 250 180 m 250 180 m 250 220 l 250 230 l 260 230 l 260 220 m 260 220 m 220 140 l 220 150 l 230 150 l 230 140 m 230 140 m 40 50 l 40 60 l 50 60 l 50 50 m 50 50 m 270 230 l 270 240 l 280 240 l 280 230 m 280 230 m 160 260 l 160 270 l 170 270 l 170 260 m 170 260 m 70 160 l 70 170 l 80 170 l 80 160 m 80 160 m 80 190 l 80 200 l 90 200 l 90 190 m 90 190 m 60 150 l 60 160 l 70 160 l 70 150 m 70 150 m 270 130 l 270 140 l 280 140 l 280 130 m 280 130 m 70 220 l 70 230 l 80 230 l 80 220 m 80 220 m 140 180 l 140 190 l 150 190 l 150 180 m 150 180 m 120 220 l 120 230 l 130 230 l 130 220 m 130 220 m 80 250 l 80 260 l 90 260 l 90 250 m 90 250 m 150 190 l 150 200 l 160 200 l 160 190 m 160 190 m 230 270 l 230 280 l 240 280 l 240 270 m 240 270 m 110 120 l 110 130 l 120 130 l 120 120 m 120 120 m 200 170 l 200 180 l 210 180 l 210 170 m 210 170 m 170 40 l 170 50 l 180 50 l 180 40 m 180 40 m 100 200 l 100 210 l 110 210 l 110 200 m 110 200 m 230 120 l 230 130 l 240 130 l 240 120 m 240 120 m 220 40 l 220 50 l 230 50 l 230 40 m 230 40 m 190 200 l 190 210 l 200 210 l 200 200 m 200 200 m 280 120 l 280 130 l 290 130 l 290 120 m 290 120 m 190 170 l 190 180 l 200 180 l 200 170 m 200 170 m 170 170 l 170 180 l 180 180 l 180 170 m 180 170 m 240 70 l 240 80 l 250 80 l 250 70 m 250 70 m 200 200 l 200 210 l 210 210 l 210 200 m 210 200 m 220 190 l 220 200 l 230 200 l 230 190 m 230 190 m 40 180 l 40 190 l 50 190 l 50 180 m 50 180 m 60 220 l 60 230 l 70 230 l 70 220 m 70 220 m 250 250 l 250 260 l 260 260 l 260 250 m 260 250 m 250 60 l 250 70 l 260 70 l 260 60 m 260 60 m 70 150 l 70 160 l 80 160 l 80 150 m 80 150 m 270 260 l 270 270 l 280 270 l 280 260 m 280 260 m 80 160 l 80 170 l 90 170 l 90 160 m 90 160 m 60 160 l 60 170 l 70 170 l 70 160 m 70 160 m 130 80 l 130 90 l 140 90 l 140 80 m 140 80 m 140 70 l 140 80 l 150 80 l 150 70 m 150 70 m 100 180 l 100 190 l 110 190 l 110 180 m 110 180 m 180 260 l 180 270 l 190 270 l 190 260 m 190 260 m 150 140 l 150 150 l 160 150 l 160 140 m 160 140 m 40 250 l 40 260 l 50 260 l 50 250 m 50 250 m 200 140 l 200 150 l 210 150 l 210 140 m 210 140 m 180 90 l 180 100 l 190 100 l 190 90 m 190 90 m 170 70 l 170 80 l 180 80 l 180 70 m 180 70 m 160 170 l 160 180 l 170 180 l 170 170 m 170 170 m 280 220 l 280 230 l 290 230 l 290 220 m 290 220 m 220 90 l 220 100 l 230 100 l 230 90 m 230 90 m 50 200 l 50 210 l 60 210 l 60 200 m 60 200 m 280 90 l 280 100 l 290 100 l 290 90 m 290 90 m 240 250 l 240 260 l 250 260 l 250 250 m 250 250 m 170 200 l 170 210 l 180 210 l 180 200 m 180 200 m 240 40 l 240 50 l 250 50 l 250 40 m 250 40 m 40 280 l 40 290 l 50 290 l 50 280 m 50 280 m 220 200 l 220 210 l 230 210 l 230 200 m 230 200 m 40 150 l 40 160 l 50 160 l 50 150 m 50 150 m 270 250 l 270 260 l 280 260 l 280 250 m 280 250 m 70 100 l 70 110 l 80 110 l 80 100 m 80 100 m 60 60 l 60 70 l 70 70 l 70 60 m 70 60 m 120 100 l 120 110 l 130 110 l 130 100 m 130 100 m 270 100 l 270 110 l 280 110 l 280 100 m 280 100 m 260 140 l 260 150 l 270 150 l 270 140 m 270 140 m 140 130 l 140 140 l 150 140 l 150 130 m 150 130 m 100 80 l 100 90 l 110 90 l 110 80 m 110 80 m 150 80 l 150 90 l 160 90 l 160 80 m 160 80 m 200 80 l 200 90 l 210 90 l 210 80 m 210 80 m 140 230 l 140 240 l 150 240 l 150 230 m 150 230 m 40 220 l 40 230 l 50 230 l 50 220 m 50 220 m 190 140 l 190 150 l 200 150 l 200 140 m 200 140 m 180 100 l 180 110 l 190 110 l 190 100 m 190 100 m 200 270 l 200 280 l 210 280 l 210 270 m 210 270 m 240 140 l 240 150 l 250 150 l 250 140 m 250 140 m 220 100 l 220 110 l 230 110 l 230 100 m 230 100 m 40 90 l 40 100 l 50 100 l 50 90 m 50 90 m 280 60 l 280 70 l 290 70 l 290 60 m 290 60 m 190 110 l 190 120 l 200 120 l 200 110 m 200 110 m 250 150 l 250 160 l 260 160 l 260 150 m 260 150 m 170 230 l 170 240 l 180 240 l 180 230 m 180 230 m 60 280 l 60 290 l 70 290 l 70 280 m 70 280 m 50 40 l 50 50 l 60 50 l 60 40 m 60 40 m 40 120 l 40 130 l 50 130 l 50 120 m 50 120 m 260 40 l 260 50 l 270 50 l 270 40 m 270 40 m 130 170 l 130 180 l 140 180 l 140 170 m 140 170 m 90 140 l 90 150 l 100 150 l 100 140 m 100 140 m 80 100 l 80 110 l 90 110 l 90 100 m 90 100 m 70 260 l 70 270 l 80 270 l 80 260 m 80 260 m 120 260 l 120 270 l 130 270 l 130 260 m 130 260 m 100 50 l 100 60 l 110 60 l 110 50 m 110 50 m 150 70 l 150 80 l 160 80 l 160 70 m 160 70 m 130 270 l 130 280 l 140 280 l 140 270 m 140 270 m 180 160 l 180 170 l 190 170 l 190 160 m 190 160 m 100 240 l 100 250 l 110 250 l 110 240 m 110 240 m 160 80 l 160 90 l 170 90 l 170 80 m 170 80 m 150 240 l 150 250 l 160 250 l 160 240 m 160 240 m 210 160 l 210 170 l 220 170 l 220 160 m 220 160 m 190 130 l 190 140 l 200 140 l 200 130 m 200 130 m 180 70 l 180 80 l 190 80 l 190 70 m 190 70 m 170 130 l 170 140 l 180 140 l 180 130 m 180 130 m 280 160 l 280 170 l 290 170 l 290 160 m 290 160 m 200 240 l 200 250 l 210 250 l 210 240 m 210 240 m 160 270 l 160 280 l 170 280 l 170 270 m 170 270 m 40 60 l 40 70 l 50 70 l 50 60 m 50 60 m 250 180 l 250 190 l 260 190 l 260 180 m 260 180 m 170 260 l 170 270 l 180 270 l 180 260 m 180 260 m 70 40 l 70 50 l 80 50 l 80 40 m 80 40 m 60 120 l 60 130 l 70 130 l 70 120 m 70 120 m 120 40 l 120 50 l 130 50 l 130 40 m 130 40 m 70 250 l 70 260 l 80 260 l 80 250 m 80 250 m 140 190 l 140 200 l 150 200 l 150 190 m 150 190 m 100 60 l 100 70 l 110 70 l 110 60 m 110 60 m 80 260 l 80 270 l 90 270 l 90 260 m 90 260 m 130 220 l 130 230 l 140 230 l 140 220 m 140 220 m 190 230 l 190 240 l 200 240 l 200 230 m 200 230 m 280 260 l 280 270 l 290 270 l 290 260 m 290 260 m 240 210 l 240 220 l 250 220 l 250 210 m 250 210 m 220 50 l 220 60 l 230 60 l 230 50 m 230 50 m 280 130 l 280 140 l 290 140 l 290 130 m 290 130 m 190 160 l 190 170 l 200 170 l 200 160 m 200 160 m 200 210 l 200 220 l 210 220 l 210 210 m 210 210 m 160 240 l 160 250 l 170 250 l 170 240 m 170 240 m 250 240 l 250 250 l 260 250 l 260 240 m 260 240 m 220 160 l 220 170 l 230 170 l 230 160 m 230 160 m 190 260 l 190 270 l 200 270 l 200 260 m 200 260 m 70 140 l 70 150 l 80 150 l 80 140 m 80 140 m 50 180 l 50 190 l 60 190 l 60 180 m 60 180 m 260 180 l 260 190 l 270 190 l 270 180 m 270 180 m 80 170 l 80 180 l 90 180 l 90 170 m 90 170 m 90 40 l 90 50 l 100 50 l 100 40 m 100 40 m 80 280 l 80 290 l 90 290 l 90 280 m 90 280 m 70 200 l 70 210 l 80 210 l 80 200 m 80 200 m 140 40 l 140 50 l 150 50 l 150 40 m 150 40 m 130 280 l 130 290 l 140 290 l 140 280 m 140 280 m 120 200 l 120 210 l 130 210 l 130 200 m 130 200 m 180 270 l 180 280 l 190 280 l 190 270 m 190 270 m 40 260 l 40 270 l 50 270 l 50 260 m 50 260 m 200 150 l 200 160 l 210 160 l 210 150 m 210 150 m 110 180 l 110 190 l 120 190 l 120 180 m 120 180 m 170 60 l 170 70 l 180 70 l 180 60 m 180 60 m 160 180 l 160 190 l 170 190 l 170 180 m 170 180 m 230 100 l 230 110 l 240 110 l 240 100 m 240 100 m 220 60 l 220 70 l 230 70 l 230 60 m 230 60 m 210 140 l 210 150 l 220 150 l 220 140 m 220 140 m 190 70 l 190 80 l 200 80 l 200 70 m 200 70 m 280 100 l 280 110 l 290 110 l 290 100 m 290 100 m 260 210 l 260 220 l 270 220 l 270 210 m 270 210 m 100 220 l 100 230 l 110 230 l 110 220 m 110 220 m 60 240 l 60 250 l 70 250 l 70 240 m 70 240 m 240 260 l 240 270 l 250 270 l 250 260 m 250 260 m 260 80 l 260 90 l 270 90 l 270 80 m 270 80 m 250 80 l 250 90 l 260 90 l 260 80 m 260 80 m 70 130 l 70 140 l 80 140 l 80 130 m 80 130 m 60 70 l 60 80 l 70 80 l 70 70 m 70 70 m 50 130 l 50 140 l 60 140 l 60 130 m 60 130 m 80 60 l 80 70 l 90 70 l 90 60 m 90 60 m 100 90 l 100 100 l 110 100 l 110 90 m 110 90 m 150 110 l 150 120 l 160 120 l 160 110 m 160 110 m 200 90 l 200 100 l 210 100 l 210 90 m 210 90 m 100 120 l 100 130 l 110 130 l 110 120 m 110 120 m 180 200 l 180 210 l 190 210 l 190 200 m 190 200 m 160 40 l 160 50 l 170 50 l 170 40 m 170 40 m 150 120 l 150 130 l 160 130 l 160 120 m 160 120 m 230 200 l 230 210 l 240 210 l 240 200 m 240 200 m 40 230 l 40 240 l 50 240 l 50 230 m 50 230 m 110 170 l 110 180 l 120 180 l 120 170 m 120 170 m 180 110 l 180 120 l 190 120 l 190 110 m 190 110 m 170 90 l 170 100 l 180 100 l 180 90 m 180 90 m 190 250 l 190 260 l 200 260 l 200 250 m 200 250 m 240 200 l 240 210 l 250 210 l 250 200 m 250 200 m 50 220 l 50 230 l 60 230 l 60 220 m 60 220 m 40 100 l 40 110 l 50 110 l 50 100 m 50 100 m 280 70 l 280 80 l 290 80 l 290 70 m 290 70 m 210 250 l 210 260 l 220 260 l 220 250 m 220 250 m 250 140 l 250 150 l 260 150 l 260 140 m 260 140 m 240 100 l 240 110 l 250 110 l 250 100 m 250 100 m 220 220 l 220 230 l 230 230 l 230 220 m 230 220 m 40 130 l 40 140 l 50 140 l 50 130 m 50 130 m 70 80 l 70 90 l 80 90 l 80 80 m 80 80 m 60 80 l 60 90 l 70 90 l 70 80 m 70 80 m 130 160 l 130 170 l 140 170 l 140 160 m 140 160 m 140 150 l 140 160 l 150 160 l 150 150 m 150 150 m 130 50 l 130 60 l 140 60 l 140 50 m 140 50 m 100 100 l 100 110 l 110 110 l 110 100 m 110 100 m 90 100 l 90 110 l 100 110 l 100 100 m 100 100 m 80 220 l 80 230 l 90 230 l 90 220 m 90 220 m 150 60 l 150 70 l 160 70 l 160 60 m 160 60 m 140 100 l 140 110 l 150 110 l 150 100 m 150 100 m 100 250 l 100 260 l 110 260 l 110 250 m 110 250 m 160 90 l 160 100 l 170 100 l 170 90 m 170 90 m 150 270 l 150 280 l 160 280 l 160 270 m 160 270 m 40 200 l 40 210 l 50 210 l 50 200 m 50 200 m 190 120 l 190 130 l 200 130 l 200 120 m 200 120 m 180 40 l 180 50 l 190 50 l 190 40 m 190 40 m 280 170 l 280 180 l 290 180 l 290 170 m 290 170 m 100 280 l 100 290 l 110 290 l 110 280 m 110 280 m 230 40 l 230 50 l 240 50 l 240 40 m 240 40 m 40 70 l 40 80 l 50 80 l 50 70 m 50 70 m 280 40 l 280 50 l 290 50 l 290 40 m 290 40 m 210 200 l 210 210 l 220 210 l 220 200 m 220 200 m 200 280 l 200 290 l 210 290 l 210 280 m 210 280 m 70 180 l 70 190 l 80 190 l 80 180 m 80 180 m 250 280 l 250 290 l 260 290 l 260 280 m 260 280 m 220 270 l 220 280 l 230 280 l 230 270 m 230 270 m 260 60 l 260 70 l 270 70 l 270 60 m 270 60 m 80 130 l 80 140 l 90 140 l 90 130 m 90 130 m 70 70 l 70 80 l 80 80 l 80 70 m 80 70 m 80 80 l 80 90 l 90 90 l 90 80 m 90 80 m 70 240 l 70 250 l 80 250 l 80 240 m 80 240 m 100 70 l 100 80 l 110 80 l 110 70 m 110 70 m 150 50 l 150 60 l 160 60 l 160 50 m 160 50 m 130 210 l 130 220 l 140 220 l 140 210 m 140 210 m 110 140 l 110 150 l 120 150 l 120 140 m 120 140 m 200 190 l 200 200 l 210 200 l 210 190 m 210 190 m 100 260 l 100 270 l 110 270 l 110 260 m 110 260 m 240 220 l 240 230 l 250 230 l 250 220 m 250 220 m 230 140 l 230 150 l 240 150 l 240 140 m 240 140 m 150 220 l 150 230 l 160 230 l 160 220 m 160 220 m 140 260 l 140 270 l 150 270 l 150 260 m 150 260 m 280 140 l 280 150 l 290 150 l 290 140 m 290 140 m 200 220 l 200 230 l 210 230 l 210 220 m 210 220 m 260 250 l 260 260 l 270 260 l 270 250 m 270 250 m 160 250 l 160 260 l 170 260 l 170 250 m 170 250 m 60 200 l 60 210 l 70 210 l 70 200 m 70 200 m 220 170 l 220 180 l 230 180 l 230 170 m 230 170 m 40 40 l 40 50 l 50 50 l 50 40 m 50 40 m 270 200 l 270 210 l 280 210 l 280 200 m 280 200 m 50 280 l 50 290 l 60 290 l 60 280 m 60 280 m 250 40 l 250 50 l 260 50 l 260 40 m 260 40 m 170 280 l 170 290 l 180 290 l 180 280 m 180 280 m 50 170 l 50 180 l 60 180 l 60 170 m 60 170 m 120 150 l 120 160 l 130 160 l 130 150 m 130 150 m 220 280 l 220 290 l 230 290 l 230 280 m 230 280 m 80 180 l 80 190 l 90 190 l 90 180 m 90 180 m 60 140 l 60 150 l 70 150 l 70 140 m 70 140 m 130 140 l 130 150 l 140 150 l 140 140 m 140 140 m 120 210 l 120 220 l 130 220 l 130 210 m 130 210 m 100 160 l 100 170 l 110 170 l 110 160 m 110 160 m 80 240 l 80 250 l 90 250 l 90 240 m 90 240 m 150 160 l 150 170 l 160 170 l 160 160 m 160 160 m 230 240 l 230 250 l 240 250 l 240 240 m 240 240 m 40 270 l 40 280 l 50 280 l 50 270 m 50 270 m 280 240 l 280 250 l 290 250 l 290 240 m 290 240 m 180 150 l 180 160 l 190 160 l 190 150 m 190 150 m 170 50 l 170 60 l 180 60 l 180 50 m 180 50 m 160 190 l 160 200 l 170 200 l 170 190 m 170 190 m 230 130 l 230 140 l 240 140 l 240 130 m 240 130 m 220 70 l 220 80 l 230 80 l 230 70 m 230 70 m 210 130 l 210 140 l 220 140 l 220 130 m 220 130 m 100 230 l 100 240 l 110 240 l 110 230 m 110 230 m 240 270 l 240 280 l 250 280 l 250 270 m 250 270 m 240 60 l 240 70 l 250 70 l 250 60 m 250 60 m 60 250 l 60 260 l 70 260 l 70 250 m 70 250 m 250 70 l 250 80 l 260 80 l 260 70 m 260 70 m 190 270 l 190 280 l 200 280 l 200 270 m 200 270 m 60 40 l 60 50 l 70 50 l 70 40 m 70 40 m 270 40 l 270 50 l 280 50 l 280 40 m 280 40 m 260 120 l 260 130 l 270 130 l 270 120 m 270 120 m 80 70 l 80 80 l 90 80 l 90 70 m 90 70 m 60 190 l 60 200 l 70 200 l 70 190 m 70 190 m 270 170 l 270 180 l 280 180 l 280 170 m 280 170
她叫儿子小麦
She referred to our son as Junior.
我们说好不那样叫他的
We agreed we'd never call him that.
app.YYeTs.com
官方网站下载 : 人人影视Pro
他在引诱你  迈克尔
He's baiting you, Michael.
他得逞了
It worked.
纽约州  伊萨卡
嗨  小子
Hey, buddy.
妈妈在哪
Where's mom?
你在学校时
I, uh, dropped her off at work
我送她去上班了
while you were at school.
那艘海盗船画得真好
That is quite a pirate ship.
不过桅杆太靠前
Although it would be a little hard
有些不利于航行
to sail with the mast that far forward.
可能会翻船
Your ship might tip over.
桅杆必须在那  这不只是一艘船
The mast has to be there. It's not just a ship--
其实是一幅藏宝图
it's a treasure map.
什么意思
What do you mean?
是给吉米的  我们相互藏乐高玩具玩
It's for Jimmy. We hide Legos for each other.
我总能找到他的
I always find his.
但他却老是找不到我的
He doesn't always find mine.
等等
Wait a second,
这张图怎么会是地图
how is this drawing a map?
这里是公园
This is the park.
那里是游乐场
That's the playground.
这是人行道
And this is the sidewalk.
太厉害了
Impressive.
你给这幅画加了密
You put a code in the drawing.
那么你把乐高藏在哪了
So, okay, where did you hide the Legos?
这些大炮是公园里的水池
These cannons are pools at the park.
但多了一个  在沙坑里
But there's an extra one, in the sand.
我把乐高埋在了那里
That's where I buried the Legos.
做得好  麦克
Well done, Mike.
做得好
Well done.
我联系了所有人  我用尽了美国的人脉
I've tried everyone. I'm out of resources in the States.
用尽了所有的关系  所有能去确认
All my contacts. People who can go and check on them,
他们没事的人
make sure they're okay.
林肯  我必须回家
Linc, I got to get home.
我不能再在货船上待两周时间
I can't spend another two weeks on a cargo ship.
我的妻儿都在他手上
He's got my wife and kid.
也许有别的方法
There may be another way.
你告诉了我你过去七年的经历
You told me about the last seven years of your life.
还没告诉你我的
Haven't told you about mine.
莎拉被赦免后  她离开了巴拿马
After Sara got exonerated, she left Panama.
我和索菲娅留了下来  开了一家潜水用具店
Me and Sofia stayed behind and opened a dive shop.
后来我们分了手  一切都变糟了
We broke up, and everything went to hell.
当时没有你的阻止  等到我自己发觉时
You weren't there to stop me, so before I knew it,
我重操了旧业  干些奇怪的活儿
I was in the old hood, doing odd jobs.
什么叫奇怪的活儿
Odd jobs meaning what?
把东西从一个地方送到另一个地方
Moving things from point A to point B.
给卢卡·阿布鲁齐做事
For Luca Abruzzi.
约翰·阿布鲁齐的儿子
John Abruzzi's son.
没错
Yeah.
当时我只想快速挣钱来重新开始生活
I just wanted some quick cash to kick-start my life.
他们让我别看箱子的东西
They told me not to look in the boxes.
但我还是看了
But I looked in the boxes.
他们从欧洲走私出来的芬太尼[止痛药可制毒]
The amount of fentanyl they're smuggling out of Europe--
每个箱子里都有成千上万颗药丸
tens of thousands of pills in every box--
这是祸害人命啊
it's just killing people.
于是我把一个箱子扔进了垃圾箱
So I dumped a box in a Dumpster,
价值10万美元
100 grand's worth.
现在你欠了阿布鲁齐的儿子一大笔债
Now you're in hock to Abruzzi's son.
没错  他想杀了我
Yeah. He wants to kill me.
但这可能是快速回到美国的捷径
But maybe it's a way to get back to the States real fast.
纽约
你胆真肥  布鲁斯
You got balls, Burrows.
你真觉得我想帮你吗
You actually think I want to help you?
如果我给你10万美元呢
What if I can get you the $100K?
十万美元
$100k?
你打算怎么筹到这笔钱
How are you gonna come up with that
在芝加哥的小巷里摸爬滚打吗
crawling around the back alleys of Chicago?
我不在芝加哥  我在马赛
I'm not in Chicago. I'm in Marseilles.
-马赛  -是的
- Marseilles? - Yeah.
我做了几笔生意  我手头有10万美元
I've been working on a couple deals. I got $100K in my hand.
但我想要脱身
But I want off the hook.
当然了  要不你过来亲手把钱给我
Sure you do. How about you get over here and hand it to me?
这就是我打给你的原因
That's why I'm calling.
我要神不知鬼不觉地溜进美国
I need to sneak into the States invisible,
就像你的毒品一样
like your pills.
你的那些从欧洲出发的飞机
Those flights you got coming out of Europe--
那些运芬太尼[止痛药可制毒]的飞机  给我留几个位子
the fentanyl flights-- I need a few seats.
这样吧
I'll tell you what.
我来联系一下
I'll make a few calls.
因为要么我见到你时  你把钱给我
'Cause either I'm gonna see you and get that money,
要么我见到你时  你的下场会更难看
or I'm gonna see you, and you're gonna get something a whole lot worse.
不敢相信我又要这么虐自己
I can't believe I'm doing this to myself again.
区别在于  这次你不是一个人在战斗
Difference is this time, you're not alone.
天啊  这东西真恶心
God, these things are disgusting.
它叫什么来着
What they call 'em again?
血肠
Boudin noir.
我不确定里面有什么
Not sure what's in them.
我觉得你的法语没有你想像中那么好
I don't think your French is as good as you think it is.
没吃蜗牛你就知足吧
Yo, be happy you're not eating snails.
恐怖分子登上货船
卡尼尔·乌提斯或在船上
你觉得他们发现了吗
Do you think they noticed?
别抱侥幸心理
Let's not take any chances.
伙计们
Guys.
你们的照片上新闻了
Your faces were on the news.
如果有人看到你  这事就完蛋了
Somebody sees you, this thing is over.
-我们得走了  兄弟  -我们该走了
- We got to move, papi. - We got to go.
等等  卢卡
Hold. Luca.
如果你午夜之前能到里昂
If you can get to Lyon by midnight,
我就能安排你上飞机
I can get you on a flight.
我在纽约有个仓库  你来找我吗
I got a warehouse in New York. You're coming to me?
我们会去的
We'll be there.
我不确定我到底
Can't decide whether I want you
希望你有没有那笔钱  布鲁斯
to have that money or not, Burrows.
杀了你或许能让我更爽
Killing you might be a lot more satisfying.
现在我们知道他们躲过了地中海的飞弹攻击
Now we know they survived the strike in the Mediterranean.
我们很确信他会回伊萨卡
We can be pretty sure he's coming back to Ithaca.
我需要一些解释
I need some clarification.
他为什么要回这里
Why would he come back here...
回美国
to the States
他在这里的话
when he's more wanted here
被抓的风险更高
than anywhere else in the world?
没错
Of course.
是因为他们
Because of them.
他在为我卖命之前  有自己的生活
He had a life before he worked for me,
有自己的名字  迈克尔·斯科菲尔德
a name-- Michael Scofield.
有自己的家庭
A family.
当他走了之后  结果是我在照料他们
And when he went away, I ended up looking after them.
结果... 我爱上了他们
Ended up... falling for them.
他想杀了我
He wants to kill me.
他认为我偷走了他的生活  毁了他
He thinks I stole his life, ruined him,
这就说到了他的精神分裂了
which speaks to his dissociative mind.
我是说  他是杀人犯  叛徒  恐怖分子
I mean, he's a murderer, a turncoat, a terrorist.
但我们可以利用这一点
But we'll use it.
如果有必要  我来当诱饵
I'll be the bait if I have to.
以便我们能着手彻底干掉他
So we can go about taking him down once and for all.
他不会就这样在这里晃荡的
He's not just gonna stroll in here.
他太聪明了
He's too clever for that.
所以我们请了一位更聪明的
That's why we got someone even more clever.
梭罗吗
Thoreau?
这家伙是个胆小鬼
Guy's a pencil neck.
是个了解斯科菲尔德计划的胆小鬼
A pencil neck with insight into Scofield's plan.
这样你才能当好汉
So you, in turn, can be the hammer.
这张截图来自他从沙漠发出的聊天视频
Screen-grab of the Skype transmission he sent from the desert.
通过服务器将它传给叫"蓝色夏威夷"的人
He routed the image through a server to this BlueHawaii guy,
但也可能通过子路线秘密传送给
but it could have been secretly subrouted to another,
一名尚不知身份的人来使用其中加密的信息
yet unknown, recipient to use the information encoded in it.
什么信息
Information?
真的很了不起
It's actually incredible.
图片用阿拉伯语加密  包含了很多信息
Encrypted in the Arabic, the images are all sorts of stuff.
乍一看  太平常不过了
Apparently, mundane as hell.
动物园的参观时间
Visiting hours for zoos,
已失效的互联网留言板链接
links to defunct message boards on the Internet.
什么留言板
What message boards?
Truesnuff.com  Hunterspycamporn.com
Truesnuff.com, Hunterspycamporn.com,
两个网站上都有... 这个
both of which carry... this.
哈伦·盖恩斯谋杀案的照片
Images of the Harlan Gaines murder.
这混蛋干嘛丢这些照片出来嘲讽我们
What's the bastard doing rubbing that in our faces?
有那么多信息可以加密  为什么选这个
Of all the things to encrypt, why that?
你从这里面发现了什么
What's that get you?
从隐写术的角度看  有很多发现
Stegaonographically, a lot.
隐写术是一种将信息隐藏在
Steganography is the practice of concealing information
组成数字文件的代码中的技术
in the code that makes up digital files.
俄罗斯用  中国用  大家都会用
Russians do it, Chinese, everybody.
他可能觉得如果有人能看见这些
He's probably thinking if anyone sees this,
他们能看见的也仅此而已
this'll be as far as they'll look.
但我已经深入到图像内部
But I'm already going inside the image,
破解了构成图像的数据
breaking down the data that comprises it.
我脑袋都晕了
This is making my head spin.
重点是如果我们使用大数据  人工智能
Point is we put big data, AI on this,
很快就能破解里面隐藏的任何代码
we can crunch any codes hidden in there pretty quickly.
这就是我正在做的
And that's what I'm doing.
好样的
Nice work,
但事实是如果我已做好自己的本分
but the truth is if I've done my job,
或许他就会先暴露自己的意图
he may reveal his intentions to us first.
因为现在我已迫使他偏离计划这么远
Because I've got him so far off his game now,
他会过早开始行动
he'll start to play his cards too early...
泰迪[即茶包哥]
Teddy.
现在知道神秘捐助人就是我了吧
不过天上不会掉馅饼
总有一天  你得为我出力  为他人所不能为
信封内的信息将改变你的人生
看了你就明白了
但作为回报  你必须杀一个人[双关语  选择新的人生]
- 迈克尔
"但作为回报  你必须杀一个人"[双关语  选择新的人生]
"But in return, you must take a life."
甚至在电脑计算出结果之前
...show us what the tattoos mean
就能告诉我们纹身的含义
even before the computers will,
以及所有他准备招募来参加行动的人
and all the people he'll be enlisting for the fight.
你得打给这个法国的付费电话
You have to call this pay phone in France.
等等  芝加哥吗  我还以为要和你一起走
Wait. Chicago? I thought I was going with you.
等你明白为什么你是我的得力干将再说
Not until you find out why you're my whip-hand.
我必须要到芝加哥才能明白吗
I have to go to Chicago to find that out?
一路平安
Safe travels.
在他如此繁复的计划之中
In the grandiosity of his plan,
他会看不清最简单的细节
he'll lose sight of the simplest details.
他昨晚给我发信息所用的手机
The phone he texted me with
位置定位在法国里昂
was located in Lyon, France last night.
晚上11点51分时在机场航站楼关机
It was turned off in an airport terminal at 11:51 P.M...
再过20分钟就有架直飞纽约的航班
...20 minutes before a direct flight to New York
你们就去那守株待兔
where you'll be waiting for him
彻底结束这场游戏
to put this game to bed for good.
纽约州  肯尼迪国际机场
前往佛罗里达州迈阿密市的
Flight 290 to Miami, Florida will now
290次航班现在将离开B24号登机口
depart from gate B24.
他刚刚重新开机了
He just powered back up.
肯尼迪国际机场
我们找到他了
We got him.
小心
Look out!
机尾
Back of the plane.
抱歉  抱歉  你们不可以...
Uh, excuse me! Excuse me. You're not allowed...
看来游戏还在继续
Looks like the game's still going.
纽约州北部  威尔莫特市立机场
你只靠贿赂机场的小官员
It's impressive how you get these drugs in the country
就能把这些毒品运进国内也是没谁了
just by bribing small-time airport officials.
我猜你在这放了
I'm guessing you got about
价值五百万的芬太尼
five million bucks worth of fentanyl in here.
那又怎样
So what?
你和你弟是要来教我做人吗
You and your brother here are gonna lecture me?
我们其实是在讨论
We were actually debating on whether
要不要给你那十万
I should give you the 100K or not.
他说这钱沾着无辜者的血
He says it's blood money.
我同意
I agree.
闭上嘴直接把钱给我怎样  布鲁斯
How about you just shut up and pay me, Burrows?
我没钱
I don't have it.
抓住他的人  把他们带到后面枪毙
Grab his guys, bring 'em to the back and shoot 'em.
你不想往你的拘捕令上再添谋杀罪吧
I don't think you want to add murder to your arrest warrant.
等一下
Wait.
什么拘捕令
Arrest warrant?
外面的那个家伙
That guy out there
是缉毒局的人
is a DEA informant.
他现在完全听我们的
We have him in our pocket.
他欠我们的  他有三车的
He owes us. He's got three vans
探员在等着他的电话
full of agents that are waiting for his call.
他们会如雨点般扑向你和你藏的毒品
They're gonna rain down on you and your pills.
除非你不再追究我哥的欠款
Unless you forgive my brother's debt.
那么我们的线人就不会打电话
Then our informant won't make the call.
让你弟来给你撑腰吗
Have your brother fighting your battles, do you?
不是
No.
不如让你的人放下枪
Why don't you tell your guys to drop the guns,
然后我们单挑
and you and I can have it out?
你怎么说  卢卡
What do you say, Luca?
把外面那人赶跑
Scare that guy off.
把这些人带到后面去
Bring these guys to the back.
他们一旦有动作  他就会打电话
They make a move, he makes a call.
真的吗  我觉得你在唬我
Yeah? I think you're bluffing.
我可警告过你了
I warned you.
有人入侵
We got company.
你开枪杀我们  现在就有几十个目击者了
You shoot us, there's dozens of witnesses now.
我们走
Let's go.
只要让他们看到缉毒局的帽子和几辆SUV
All they had to see were DEA hats and SUVs,
他们就被吓跑了
and they were gone.
久仰大名啊  迈克尔·斯科菲尔德
Famous Michael Scofield.
希巴  谢谢你做的一切
Sheba. Thank you for everything.
你都不知道我见到你回家有多高兴
You have no idea how happy I am to see you back home.
我们还没到家
We're not home yet.
好吧  下一步怎么办
All right, so what's next?
我们怎么抓到这个混蛋
How do we get this son of a bitch?
不是"我们"做什么
We don't do anything.
你的使命已经完成了
Your part is over.
不  不  不
No, no, no, no, no, no.
戏耍一回阿布鲁齐的儿子是一回事
Tricking Abruzzi's kid is one thing.
但波塞冬  他见过你的脸
Poseidon-- he knows your face.
自从你到了也门就一直在追踪你
Been tracking you since you went to Yemen.
你一直是名勇士  我欠你一个人情
You've been a warrior, and I owe you.
但现在你的脸会拖累你和你的家人
But your face is a liability now to you and your family.
我不想让你涉险
I don't want you to risk that.
他们或许认得他的脸  但认不出我的
They may know his face, but they don't know mine.
出其不意  攻其不备嘛
It's the punch you don't see coming that knocks you out.
这才是我的希巴
That's my Sheba.
你照顾好她  行吗
You take care of her, all right?
你是说让我照顾好他吧
I take care of him, you mean.
好兄弟
I love you, brother.
Love you, too.
-注意安全  好吗  -你也是
- Be safe, okay? - ‭You, too.
-再见  -好的  那么...
- Bye. - ‭All right. Well...
再有事需要我
when you need me again,
你知道去哪里找我
you know where to find me.
我们会在下午四点转移她
We'll transport her at 1600 hours.
在那之前保持低调  谢谢
Lay low until then. Thank you.
刚才那一幕你不介意吗
That doesn't bother you-- what you just saw in there?
把老婆关在地下室
Down in the basement with his wife,
那个他口口声声说深爱的女人
the woman he says he fell for?
别说了
Stop.
干完这次我就退出"21号空间"
I'm done with 21-Void after this.
等我们抓到斯科菲尔德  乌提斯
After we get Scofield... Outis--
管他叫什么
whatever his name is--
我退出
I'm done.
我就只是想抓到杀害盖恩斯的凶手
That's all I ever wanted, to get Gaines' killer,
但他在里面做的事
but what he's got going on in there--
那可不正常
that's not normal.
那是私仇  太变态了
It's personal. Something sicker.
没人能离开"21号空间"  梵  你很知道
There's no leaving 21-Void, Van. You know that.
他雇我们  因为我们是顶尖高手
He hired us because we are the best.
我们想做什么都可以
We can do whatever we want.
如果干完这次后我们想要人间蒸发
And if we want to disappear after this...
我们就可以销声匿迹
we can disappear.
不可能逃走的
There's no getting out.
如果你那么想...
If you think that way...
那你也沦为了一名"囚徒"
then you're a prisoner, too.
门口那人说他们到这里五分钟之后
The guy at the gate said the vehicles split
那些车就分开走了
five minutes after they got here.
五分钟吗
Five minutes?
哪里不太对
Something ain't right.
货还在这里没动
The product is still here.
走
Come on.
这些全都是他们预谋好的
It was all staged.
高明啊
Clever.
但布鲁斯会为此丢了小命的
But Burrows is gonna die for it.
我不知道我们该怎么找到他
I don't know how we're gonna find him.
他已跑得不见踪影了
He's in the wind.
那可不一定
Maybe not.
易通路卡的接收器
EZ Pass transponders.
桑特拉在高速运输管理局有认识的人
Santora's got a guy at transit authority.
他肯定能告诉我们他们何时上了哪条路
I bet you he can tell us what roads they've been taking and when.
接下来就要靠我们巡查周边
Then it's up to us to comb the neighborhoods,
找到那些车
find the vehicles,
然后一枪打死那个贱人
and put a bullet in that son of a bitch once and for all.
我有个奇怪的要求
I got a weird request.
如果我给你一些坐标  你能带我去吗
If I give you some coordinates, can you take me to 'em?
我试试
See what I can do.
不行  除非这辆车自带浮船  否则没门
No. Unless this cab's got pontoons, ain't gonna happen.
这坐标在密歇根湖中央
These coordinates are in the middle of Lake Michigan.
纽约州  伊萨卡
就是这里了
This is it.
没有灯光
No lights.
我觉得他们不在这里  迈克尔
I don't think they're here, Michael.
除非他就是想让我们这么想
Unless that's what he wants us to think.
走吧
Come on.
准备好尽快带我们逃跑
Get ready to get us out of here as fast as you can.
林肯
Linc.
多加小心
Be careful.
谢了
Thanks.
怎么了
What's wrong?
怪不得莎拉从来都不回信
That's why Sara never responded.
我不能跟任何人联系
I wasn't allowed to contact anyone,
但她是我妻子
but she was my wife.
莎拉·斯科菲尔德收
纽约州  伊萨卡  内斯特路1990号
邮编  14850
我使用本以为只有她会知道的方法联系她
I reached out to her in a way I thought only she would know.
但他也知道
But he knew my ways, too.
什么也没有
Nothing.
莎拉
我在伊萨卡
你在干什么
What are you doing?
谢天谢地
那不是莎拉  迈克尔
That's not Sara, Michael.
他不知道我察觉了
He doesn't know I know that.
你和麦克明天能出发吗
能  要我们去哪
记得我还欠你一顿晚餐吗
菲力牛排
这回答是对的  她还活着
That's the right answer. She's alive.
他肯定跟她在一起
He must be right there with her.
我要安排一次见面
I'm gonna set a meeting.
什么  你就这么亲自过去露个脸吗
And what, you're just gonna show up and show your face?
没错
Yes.
雪城的莫雷利牛排餐馆  正午碰面
那表示波塞冬也会露面
That means Poseidon has to show his face, too.
游戏的最终局开启
And the endgame begins.
纽约州  雪城
莫雷利牛排餐馆
正午了  老板
It's high noon, boss.
我没看见他
I'm not seeing him.
那就对了  他是在等我们
And you shouldn't. He's waiting for us
走第一步棋
to push the first piece out onto the board.
也就是我吗
Which would be me?
也许不是
Maybe not.
黑色SUV
Black SUV.
有什么需要帮忙的吗
Something I can help you with?
接车服务  我来接一位女士和小孩
Car service. I'm here to pick up a lady and child.
他们上别的车走了  你走吧
They got another ride. Hit the road.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
快走
Hit the road.
记下那辆黑色SUV
Mark the black SUV.
不用  那只是让你露个面用的
No need. They were just here to make you show your face.
现在走开  快
Walk away, please. Now.
好  表现出有点小慌张的样子
Okay, act the tiniest bit flustered.
现在重复我说的话  大声点让人听到
Now repeat these words back to me loud enough to be heard:
"他们没出现"
"They didn't show."
"我现在回你那里去"
"I'm coming back to you now."
他们没出现
They didn't show.
我现在回你那里去
I'm coming back to you now.
游戏上演了
Now we have a game.
他现在已经暴露了他哥
He's already revealed his brother,
他最大的一颗棋子
his biggest piece.
很快他就得露脸了
Soon he'll have to show his face.
负责跟踪的探员  拿下他
Trailer, please take him down.
车库入口  限高2米
搞什么
What the...?
我跟丢了
I lost him.
你能听见我吗
Can you hear me?
该死的
Damn it.
没信号
No signal.
你来这里做什么
What are you doing here?
我在车库没信号
I lost reception in the garage.
该死的  你中计了
Damn it, you fell right into it.
现在他们找到我们了
Now they've got a mark on us.
黑色轿车
Black sedan.
他正往西走
He's heading west.
别
Please!
请别开枪
Please, don't shoot.
你还好吗
You okay?
毁了我的国家的狗杂种长这个样子
So that's what the dog who's destroying my country looks like.
说话
Talk to me.
迈克尔  我们找到车了
Michael, we found the car.
我们在第三大道和华盛顿大道旁的路边拐角
We're on the corner of Third and Washington by an alley.
快过来
Get here now.
他带走了莎拉  但我们没看见她
He had Sara with him but we couldn't see her.
什么叫你没看见她
What do you mean you couldn't see her?
我们的视角看不到
There's no way we could have.
我的天  莎拉
Oh, my God. Sara.
当时后座上没人吗
There was no one in the backseat?
不  车窗涂了银膜  我们看不到
No, the windows were blacked out-- we couldn't see.
这是什么
What's that?
我儿子画的
My son did this.
他很棒
He's good.
这上面可能会有些什么
There might be something here.
这是一艘船
It's a ship.
一艘海盗船  上面有三个海盗
A pirate ship with three pirates--
男人  女人  和一个小男孩
man, woman and a boy.
就是我  莎拉  还有麦克
That's me, Sara and... Mike.
你觉得那是什么
What do you think that is?
这是... 是条多头蛇
It's a... it's a many-headed hydra
正往上爬伺机攻击
reaching up to attack.
是在说雅各布吗
Think it's Jacob?
八九不离十
Must be.
这是一条讯息
This is a message.
你是说麦克在画里暗藏了讯息
You're telling me Mikey's left something encoded in that?
是啊  他天生就懂
Yeah. Yeah, it's encoded in him.
他遗传了我的基因
He's got my DNA.
可他连你要来都不知道
He didn't even know you were coming.
肯定是莎拉告诉他的  我不知道
Sara must have told him. I don't know.
她肯定跟他说了我要来
She must have told him I was coming.
这里面绝对有什么  百分百有
There's definitely something here. Definitely.
那是什么
What is it?
卢卡的一个手下
It's one of Luca's guys.
什么
What?
他是怎么追踪我们到这的
How the hell did he track us here?
我不知道
I don't know.
我只知道所有的因果报应
All I know is all the chickens are coming home
都挑了这个最糟糕的时候找上门来
to roost at the worst possible time.
我们得赶紧走
We got to go.
哥
Linc?
我懂了
I got it.
这艘船  这艘大帆船
This ship, this galleon.
船所在的这片水域  我刚看了地图
The body of water it's on. I looked at the map.
有片湖的轮廓和这个一模一样
There's a lake, a lake shaped exactly like it,
就在手指湖区
up in the Finger Lakes district.
"长湖"
"Long lake."
这个X标记应该是指长湖的东岸
This X would be on the east shore of that lake.
他是在告诉我们他的位置
He's telling us where he is.
我在想你是不是疯了
I'm trying to figure out if you lost your mind or not.
只有一个办法能搞清楚了
There's only one way to find out.
什么
‭What?
-你得回布法罗去  -什么
- You're going back to Buffalo. - ‭What?!
我要你和你的家人待在一起  照看难民
I want you to be with your family, look after the refugees.
林肯  我也是这件事的一员
Linc, I'm a part of this fight, too...
这是什么意思
What was that?
吻别
It's good-bye.
如果你出事  我永远都不会原谅自己
I could never forgive myself if something happened to you.
芝加哥  伊利诺斯州
密歇根湖沿岸
有什么能帮你吗
Can I help you?
有
Yeah.
我能租条船吗
Can I rent a boat?
我想坐着去湖上转转
I want to take one out on the lake.
但作为回报  你必须杀一个人[双关语  选择新的人生]
- 迈克尔
正在录音
一直在思考
Been thinkin'.
上帝...
God...
我一直在思考
I been thinking.
因为有笔吃亏的买卖摆在我面前
'Cause a hard bargain's been presented to me,
所以我打算动用
and I'm considering something
以前的西尔多·拜格威尔做派
that's-that's gonna seem like the old Theodore Bagwell.
正前方
北纬43度50分32秒  西经87度4分39秒
茶包哥
T-Bag.
如果它终将发生...
And if that's indeed what's coming...
它不会出自一个冷血之徒之手
...it won't be the work of a cold-blooded man.
不是为了罪孽...
And it won't be for sin...
亦不是为了仇恨
...or for hate.
如果鲜血沾染了我的双手
If there's blood on my hands,
世人须知...
know this, world...
这是为了爱
...it'll be for love.
还好吗  小家伙
How you doing, buddy?
我在湖边小屋待够了
I'm sick of the lake house.
我想回家
I want to go home.
我知道  我知道
I know. I know.
我们马上就会回家了
We'll go home soon.
别担心
Don't worry.
妈妈还好吗
Is Mom okay?
她...
She's, uh...
她有点不舒服
she's a little under the weather.
她在休息
She's just resting.
一切都会好起来  孩子
Everything will be fine, kiddo.
很快一切就会恢复如常了  好吗
Everything will be back to normal soon enough, okay?
迈克尔  去救他  我会准备好
Michael, go get him. And I'll be ready.
谢了  伙计  很好玩
Thanks, man, that was fun.
不客气  随时效劳
‭Yeah, anytime.
好  谢谢
Yeah, great. Thank you.
维普是个怎样尊贵的名字
What kind of honorific is Whip?
你是谁
Who's asking?
注定卷入此事之人
A man drawn into this by destiny.
好吧  你走开好吗
Okay. How about you take off?
我可不是随便就对跟我搭讪的人
I don't exactly cotton to strange men coming up to me
有好感的  懂吗
in the middle of the night, you know?
只有一个人叫我维普  但那人不是你
Only one person calls me Whip-- you ain't him.
就是"无名氏"这么叫你的
"Nobody" calls you that.
[即希腊语"乌提斯"  即迈克尔]
给了我这只手的那位"无名氏"
Man who gave me this hand. Nobody.
卡尼尔·乌提斯
Kaniel Outis.
或对于像我们这些认识他的人来说
Or for those of us who know him,
迈克尔·斯科菲尔德
Michael Scofield.
你是谁
Who are you?
我们都有昵称  不是吗
We all got handles, don't we?
乌提斯  茶包哥  维普
Outis. T-Bag. Whip.
但你的真名叫戴夫·马丁  对吗
But you're Dave Martin, aren't you?
你是怎么知道的
How'd you know that?
你最好赶紧说清楚  老家伙
You better start talking, old man.
你最好别我老子吵
You don't want to tangle with this.
彼此彼此
Neither do you.
你要的答案都在这里面  好吗
All your answers are right in here, all right?
西弗吉尼亚一家酒吧
West Virginia honky-tonk,
1991年  有个漂亮的女服务员
1991, pretty waitress,
关门后我们就两人世界嘿嘿嘿了
bunch of personal business between us after closing,
接着因为有个臭条子死盯着我而惹了麻烦
and then I git, 'cause Johnny Law's breathing down my neck.
当时也没有她的联系地址
Lacking a forwarding address,
所以我再也没有得到她的音讯
I never heard from her again.
你到底想说什么
What are you trying to tell me?
当时斯科菲尔德在各个监狱里搜寻搭档
Scofield was looking for a partner, combing prisons,
想找一个独自生存能力强的人
looking for someone who could handle himself.
因为你与生俱来的生存本能
And with your innate ability to thrive,
连最糟糕的监狱里也能混得风生水起
rising to the top in even the worst of cages,
你让他想起了一个人
you reminded him of a certain someone.
于是他做了点调查
And so he did a little research.
想知道我们都想知道的事
Wanted to know what we all want to know.
到底是你学来的
Did you learn it...
还是与生俱来的
or was it ingrained in you?
是你与生俱来的  孩子
It was ingrained in you, son.
是我传给你的
You got it from me.
林肯  他在这
Linc, he's here.
-我儿子  -感谢上帝
- My son. - Thank God.
等等
Hold on.
Hold up.
雅各布估计要回来了
I think Jacob's coming back.
真不敢相信我见到我儿子了
I can't believe I'm seeing my son.
有点不对劲
Something's wrong.
萨拉也在  但是...
Sara's here, but...
-有点不对劲  -别行动  他要回来了
- something's wrong. - Don't do anything. He's coming back.
我要进去
I'm going in.
不是雅各布
It's not Jacob.
安全了
You're clear.
去救你家人  去救你儿子
Get your family. Get your son.
布鲁斯
Burrows!
麦克
Hi, Mike.
你知道我是谁吗
You know who I am?
我收到了你的地图
I got your map.
我会救你和你妈妈出去
I'm gonna get you and your mother out of here.
我... 我没画过地图
I... I didn't draw a map.
-还有人和妈妈在这里吗    -不是...
- Is someone in there with your mom? - It's not...
我们得快跑
We need to run.